ELISABET VAZQUEZ

Los Angeles, CA | (+1) 310-254-0759 | elisabetvz.com | elisabetv.design@gmail.com | linkedin.com/in/elisabetv | EU Work Permit | Available for Freelance Projects | Creative Services | Open to Full-Time or Contractor Position

PROFESSIONAL SUMMARY

I'm an interdisciplinary creative focused on Strategy, Art Direction and Design, specializing in branding and advertising. I acquired a Political Science degree from UCL exploring a range of subjects, mainly focused on social psychology, cognitive approaches to decision making, strategic project management, international affairs, and economics. My diverse background has sharpened my problem-solving skills to provide effective innovative solutions and maximized my adaptability to a variety of projects and industries.

EDUCATION

UCL (UNIVERSITY COLLEGE LONDON)

LONDON, UK

Bachelor of Arts - Politics, Sociology and East European Studies.

SEP. 2019 - Jun. 2022

- Grade: 2:1 (i.e.: 3.7 GPA)
- Dissertation on Cognitive Approaches to Foreign Policy Analysis

UCLA EXTENSION
Certificate, Design Communication Arts

LOS ANGELES, USA

Jun. 2021 – Aug. 2022

Certificate, Directing

MAR. 2022 - AUG. 2023

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

JUICE HOUSE (Creative Agency)

REMOTE

Social Media Marketing Lead

SEP. 2022-current

- Creative Direction, Social Planning and Management of @juicehousecreative accounts + Newsletter Design
- Content Creation + Socials, working with @itsduncanlaurence, @sofiavaldes, @trinsgby, etc.

MINA BAIE (Retail Company)

LOS ANGELES, USA

Junior Graphic Designer

SEP. 2022-DEC. 2022

• Designed Emails, GIFs for Reels, Stories and Posts. Retouched + Color Corrected Images for Web + Socials.

MOSAIC (NGO)

LOS ANGELES, USA

Creative Team Lead Jun. 2022-current

- Art Director + Lead of a team of 6, for social media content creation, Digital Design + Photography.
- Social Media Management, Planning + Campaign Development. Image Retouching, Content Curation + Copywriting.
- Graphic Design for Social Media. Supervising + training Graphics, Photography, Social + Reels Sub-teams.

Hillsong UK (NGO)

LONDON, UK

Photographer

SEP. 2019 – MAR. 2022

Providing Photography and Photo Editing for weekly events and conferences.

A21 UK (NGO, Human Trafficking Relief)

LONDON, UK

Social Media Manager

MAR. 2020–AUG. 2020

- Led a Creative Team of 5, creating graphics and copywriting for social media campaigns.
- Developed brand awareness in social channels through content management, strategy, planning and goal setting.

VOLUNTEER EXPERIENCE

TBN España (Studio, Film & TV)

MADRID, SPAIN

Iransiator

Jan. 2018–Aug. 2018

English-Spanish Translation and Subtitling of TV Episodes.

LANGUAGES

English (fluent, C2); Spanish (native); French (advanced, C1).

TECHNICAL SKILLS

Photoshop | Illustrator | InDesign | CSS | HTML | After Effects | MS Office | Excel | Power Point | Research | Scheduling | Image Retouching | Photography | Lightroom | Sketch | Social Media Management | Project Management | Copywriting

OTHER INFORMATION & CERTIFICATES

- Confident Copywriting 6-week Short Course from UAL College of Communication (2020).
- Coded and designed my own portfolio website (elisabetvz.com) using HTML and CSS.
- 1-year Leadership Program covering subjects as critical thinking, theology, personal development (2020–2021)
- Author of 'Postcards of Humanity', connecting ideas, processes and experiences for proactive reflectivity a Substack Newsletter.